I ate seven pints of ice cream this week
and was still able to maintain a caloric
deficit. Here's how I did it. I used my
Ninja Creamy to recreate some of my
favorite Ben & Jerry's flavors, but way
lower in calories and much higher in
protein. Here are five of the flavors I
made this week. That first one was
cookie dough. Just an absolute classic
vanilla ice cream with little cookie
dough bites mixed in. This one is
Netflix and chilled. One of my most
requested flavors of all time. peanut
butter base, pretzels, and brownies.
Now, this one is lights caramel action,
which was a vanilla base with cookie
dough bites, caramel, and graham
cracker. It was just absolutely insane.
Then I did a cinnamon buns recreation.
This was a cinnamon base with a Alpha
Prime Bites cinnamon roll brownie mixed
in. Tossed it in some cinnamon and sugar
to give it that bakery style feel.
Delicious. Now, this one is coffee
toffee bar crunch. One of my favorites.
Strong coffee flavored ice cream with
little crunchy heath bits mixed in.